Guide to the Class of 1968, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1968, Yale College, records
1993-2008
RU 381
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
(1 box)
The records consist of videorecordings and a special issue of the Yale Daily News documenting the 25th reunion of the Yale College Class of 1968.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1968
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research. Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of videorecordings and a special issue of the Yale Daily News documenting the 25th reunion of the Yale College Class of 1968.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Class reunions; Videotapes; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1968; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- 25th reunion issue of the Yale Daily News, 1993; Accession 1993-A-064
  - 25th reunion issue of the Yale Daily News, 1993 (Box 1)
- Class of 1968 25th reunion [videorecording], 1993; Accession 1998-A-091
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - Class of 1968 25th reunion, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
    - Duplicating master, videotape (VHS) (Box 1-D)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 1U)
- Class of 1968, Yale College, tributes to William Sloane Coffin, Jr., circa 2008; Accession 2008-A-184
  - "Splendor and Wisdom: Reverend William Sloane Coffin, Jr. and the Yale Class of 1968", circa 2008; optical disk (DVD) (Box 1)
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
      General note
      Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
  - "A Class Tribute to the Reverend William Sloane Coffin Jr" website, circa 2008; computer files (35 HTML, 1 JPG, 14 GIF, 4 RealMedia, 22 PDF, 2 WMA)